kannadaaudio.com 2003-10-10

# KannadaAudio.com ::: Privacy Policy

We at KannadaAudio.com respect the privacy concerns of the users of this site and have created this privacy policy to explain a) what information we gather from you when you visit our site, b) how we may use such information, c) your choices concerning how we may use such information and d) the security measures we take to protect such information. 

WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
Some information is collected on this site automatically through our technology, other information is collected only when you choose to give it to us.

INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US  
* Communications with Us.   
We have features where you can submit information to us (for example contacting us with a question or problem using feedback form). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.

* Communications with Friends and others.  
Our site may also have certain features that allow you to send information to others (for example "Mail a Song" form, "Send this page" form ). We will use the contact information you enter for your friends only to send the email, and then we will delete it from our system.

*Message Boards.  
If you visit a message board on this site, if any, you are solely responsible for the content of messages you send or post there. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose Personal Information (for example, your name, email address, phone number etc.) on message boards, that information can be read, collected and used by other users of these services. We may monitor traffic via electronic software or personnel but only to check for obscenity, defamation or other types of abusive language, in which case, We reserve the right to terminate your access to this site or to take other protective steps.

* Surveys.   
We may occasionally ask users to participate in surveys. Such surveys will be voluntary. They are intended to improve your user experience. Any personal information collected will be used only by us unless we specify otherwise, although we may share aggregate survey result information with others. 

AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION   
When you visit this site, certain non-personally identifying information is recorded automatically by the standard operation of our Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, IP address (IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer so that data such as the web pages you request can be sent to you. ) is gathered in order to facilitate our online operations and to assure an efficient online experience for you. We may also use or share this information for security purposes, to generate group statistics about our user community, or as required by law.

What About Cookies?  
A "cookie" is a small text file that an Internet site can place on your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can recognize your browser, store your user name and enable you to automatically log in to the Application and any Subscription Service from your computer without entering your user name each time. At this time, we don't use any cookies.

WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION  
KannadaAudio.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. KannadaAudio.com may disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties when: a). We have your consent to share the information b). We have to cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities c). we respond to subpoenas, court orders in compliance with the legal process. d). when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property.

We will occasionally release aggregate demographic information (it will not include personal information such as email address) about user trends to partners and other third parties, including third-party advertisers on the Application. We also retain aggregated log files of requested content in order to evaluate user trends. 

SECURITY  
All personal information is stored in our secure databases. Access to that information is strictly controlled and limited to certain KannadaAudio.com employees and contractors on a need-to-know basis. We want to protect the integrity of your personal information that we may have in our database.

LINKS   
We may display links to other sites within KannadaAudio.com. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

CHANGES IN THE PRIVACY POLICY  
We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes which we consider material in our privacy practices, we will notify you in this space. We may also attempt to notify you of any such material changes to our privacy practices via email or by placing a notice on our home page.

QUESTIONS  
If you have any questions related to this Privacy Policy please send us an email at webmaster@KannadaAudio.com

This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 11th, 2003.
